Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania jacobgonos@gmail.com (412) 463-4822 www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-gonos-9360a1198 www.nithub.com/JAG240

Personal Statement

Seasoned Technical Support Engineer with 6 years of experience supporting clients ensuring the best experience. Passionate programmer seeking a company to promote the development of software engineering skills. Unique perspective on software development influenced by years of experience within the Technical Support Field.

Professional Experience

Coupa Software

January 2021 - Present

Technical Support Engineer

- Accurately diagnos reported issues to provide meaningful, timely resolutions.
- Serve as the primary point of contact for the support of owned solutions and products.
- Explain technical information in clear terms to promote better understanding for non-technical users.
- Document faults and bugs for referral to development staff for use in updates.
- Design tailored solutions for customers based upon key requirements.
- Present team members with details of discovered issues and recurrent customer concerns.
- Triage customer reported issues and assign to team members for investigation.

Geek Squad

July 2016 - August 2021

Advance Repair Agent

- Researched issues experienced by clients to identify an effective repair solution.
- Adhered to company policies to ensure the preservation of client privacy.
- · Achieved an Apple repair certification permitting certification in iOS hardware and software repairs.
- Effectively communicated with clients to discuss potential effects and consequences of repairs.
- Prioritized urgent repairs while actively working on multiple tasks simultaneously to ensuring the most effective use of time.

Eloop LLC

February 2020 - May 2020

Internship

- Collaborated with teams company-wide to learn each team's workflow and responsibilities.
- Researched essential software solutions to increase work efficiency and accuracy.
- Normalized the database design for back-end ITAD ERP solution for integration with front-end portal.
- Designed a front-end ERP solution to reduce data redundancy and increase workflow efficiency.
- Assisted team with adoption and use of new software solutions.

Education

University of Pittsburgh of Greensburg 2015 - 2020

BS in Information Technology

Key Skills

				0	C#
•	•	•	•	0	HTML
•	•	•	•	0	CSS
•	•	•	•	0	SQL
•	•	•	0	0	PHP
•	•	•	0	0	JavaScript
•	•	•	0	0	Java

Certifications

March 2019

SVC-19A (Apple Service Fundamentals)

July 2022

Ruby on Rails Essentials

Projects

Horror Game

Used Unity to create a 3D horror game that utilizes state machines, graphs, and information driven AI to create an imersive environment.

Pokemon Interactive Map

Created a web application that displays key information about areas by selecting areas of the game map.